

Bragegaten 22A, 214 46 Malmö, SE (619) 857-2323 cecile.pham@gmail.com

## **Summary**

Versatile and agile creative with 9 years of experience in the marketing and advertising field. Possesses a strong and driven work ethic with an acute eye for detail who works best under pressure. Professional experience developing marketing messages and brand identity for clients from inception to fruition. Regular duties include developing and leading design presentations to drive sales as well as regular communication with clients to develop their projects. Native English speaker.

Assets

Creative	Aptitude	Logical	Agile	Flexible	Communicative
Problem Solver	Outgoing	Humor	Detail Oriented	Savvy	Time-effective

# Experience

\* References available upon request

#### Creative Director | Skyline San Diego

#### 2007-Present

Regularly wrote, designed and lead presentations from brainstorming proposals to final design in the tradeshow exhibit industry. Reviewed and proof-read final product to ensure quality. Developed and instigated procedures which streamlined the design process to improve communication with the sales team and increase interactions with clientele. Maintained and distributed the workflow through the Art Department. Trained and educated new designers and sales representatives on industry standards. Regularly worked with other managers to measure, refine and meet company goals. Continued to meet with clients and worked with sales reps to deliver a customized solution. Clientele included Kyocera, Intuit, Qualcomm, United States Border Patrol, H2O Innovations, Toray and Limelight.

#### Structural Designer | Skyline San Diego

2006-2007

Responsible for carrying marketing messages across a tradeshow environment which included floor plan, structure, large format graphics, signage, materials and surface treatments while taking into consideration functionality, traffic flow and economy. Often met with clients directly to facilitate the process and ensure an accurate solution.

#### Graphic Designer | Skyline San Diego

2002-2006

Fulfilled client needs across a multitude of mediums including brand identity, signage, brochures, e-mailers, business cards, posters, postcards, CD and DVD covers, packaging and website maintenance. Specializing in production for large format printing. Worked directly with sales team and client to come up with effective marketing solutions.

### Flash Designer | MangoCreek

2002-2002

Developed interactive flash animated CD cards and websites.

### Graphic Designer | A'lor International (Phillipe Charriol)

2000-2002

Helped brand Charriol's image by executing ad campaigns which ran in notable magazines such as Elle, Vogue, W and GQ. Other tasks included website design updates, photography, photo manipulation and development of press kits.

# Technical Knowlege

Word Quark
Excel IronCAD

Powerpoint Strata 3D Studio Photoshop Dreamweaver

Illustrator Acrobat

InDesign Flash light knowledge

### **Award**

Health Care Communicators of San Diego County 2006 Finest Gold Award Winner for Exhibits



## Education

Bachelor of Arts | Interdisciplinary Computing and the Arts | Graduated 2002 University of California San Diego | San Diego, CA USA